utdallas.edu 2007-10-28

# Privacy Policy, UT Dallas

The University of Texas at Dallas (UTD) respects your privacy. The University's main web page does not collect personal information about visitors. In particular, we do not use "cookies" to collect information.

Personal information that you provide via e-mail or through other online means will be used only for purposes necessary to serve your needs. Such might include simple responses to questions or something as complex as considering you for enrollment in the University. The service may involve redirecting your inquiry, information or comment to another person or department better suited to meeting your needs.

We may use server logs to collect information concerning your Internet connection and general information about your visit to our Web site. This information may be used to analyze trends; to create summary statistics for the purpose of determining technical design specifications; and to identify system performance or problem areas.

Some web pages at UTD may collect personal information about visitors and use that information for purposes other than those stated above. Every UTD web page that collects personal information will use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. Each web page that collects information will have a separate privacy statement that will tell you how that information is used.

**With few exceptions, you are entitled on your request to be informed about the information UTD collects about you. Under Sections 552.021 and 552.023 of the Texas Government Code, you are entitled to receive and review the information. Under Section 559.004 of the Texas Government Code, you are entitled to have UTD correct information about you that is held by us and that is incorrect, in accordance with the procedures set forth in The University of Texas System Procedures Memorandum 32. The information that UTD collects will be retained and maintained as required by Texas records retention laws (Section 441.180 et seq. of the Texas Government Code) and rules. Different types of information are kept for different periods of time.**

The "Public Information Officer" of UTD is the Vice President for Business Affairs, Dr. Calvin Jamison. He is the designated agent for coordinating responses to requests for public information appropriately submitted to UT Dallas. He can be reached at (972) 883-2213 or by fax at (972) 883-2212. 

### Social Security Statement

Your Social Security Number (SSN) or UTD Identification Number (ID) is being requested because it is a unique ID which is maintained for the purpose of accuracy in tracking information. The disclosure of such information is voluntary. Disclosure of your SSN or UTD ID is governed by the Public Information Act (Chapter 552 of the Texas Government Code).

Information Resources Policies   (Requires [Adobe Reader](http://www.adobe.com/products/acrobat/readstep2.html)).
